Are you tired of reality not glitching enough?
Do you crave deeper thoughts, but also snacks?
Welcome to the Cult of Psyche.
Still not convinced?
Apply telepathically or just follow us.
I was denied
I'm actually tired tonight, so maybe I'll be an asset
because I can't talk much and do anything.
How are you psyche?
Good.
Oh, are you with a shirt on or just a wife beater?
Oh, I see.
Yeah, there's some kind of wife beater.
Okay, are you gonna be like Perry the fairy
or are we gonna do this again?
It looks like you're getting a blow job right now.
It's your position you're in right now.
I don't know, is that a woman or a man?
Are you?
Just let me know.
Getting a little bit jealous
Are you ready for one? It looks like you're ready for one. You are all right. Wait first of all, are you are you high out of your mind?
I'm drunk. I'm not I'm not even drunk. I'm not even drunk. That's why
You know, I think like 10 bucks is fair because you got I think in the last two streams because you kept using the n-word
I do find people like eventually and you know that
I'm already one of my YouTube's banned. Fuck it, man. I'm not
Okay, well, what's your show about? It's not our show. So if you want to kick me
I'm not gonna pay money to come back, but I wish you well or whatever. I'll be quiet
I want to support the show and then like y'all also like feel good about like and give you my address and my name after
Anonymous my friend. Oh, yeah, right. Yeah, we got money on cash
Like if you want people just donate I'll fucking leave bro like it's okay. Okay. Bye
All right, bye
Asshole, bye. Don't come back. Fuck you ugly faggot. You're a piece of shit nigger
You're the asshole. What the fuck's your problem? You methhead piece of shit. He looks 70 faggot dead niggers. Fuck you
Oh my god. Oh my god. What a shocking turn of events
Reviler red got a little bit upset when I asked for like, you know
Well, now he owes a hundred dollars if he ever wants to come back, but it's not like a big loss
It's like that's why it's like people that's just like fucking piss me off like that guy
If I find them okay, they pay me and then it's like okay, I'll put up with them for another 10 minutes if they don't
They can go fuck themselves. I don't need I don't need people like him
I mean, what did he just call me? He called me methhead AIDS F-A-G-G-O-T. I mean, it's like, and then the N word again
Haitian now. Thank you. I know it's shocking. I'm sorry if that language is it was too much
I know that was it was almost too much for me, but it's like, you know, I've been called worse by better people. So I
Mean burst his objection was
Well, I'm not paying that because then you'll have my address and I'm like, well, you can if you donate with cash up
It's completely anonymous. You won't have my you'll all you'll know is you know
Cash or cash up psyche awakens. I'll know your cat. That's all they share. Oh
well, I
Lost my show. So I don't care what I say. Well, I didn't lose my show
I haven't had a full monetized program with that. I'm allowing your dumbass answer and it's like what
I'm not paying okay. Well go away, and then he's then he calls me those names. Can you just see the character of some people I?
Mean sometimes it's like not even about pay. It's like, you know
I'd like to see them change their way of approaching me about things people like KZ people like I mean, but they're just so dumb
They'll never get it. I mean I mean
I respect, really, I do respect, you know, all kinds of teachers and stuff like that, especially
special ed teachers. It is hard dealing with some of these people, right? Like Reviler Red
and KZ. I mean, it's like these are people that were licking the windows on the short bus before
it was, you know, a funny thing to say. Not to be offensive, not to be offensive. I mean, it's like
No, honestly, there are people with Down syndrome
with better manners.
I mean, it's like, or most of them do,
but they're actually like really sweet people.
Down syndrome people are cool, but you know,
I don't know, I don't know what kind of,
what is these people's problem?
You just think, okay, so do I have a special surprise
for you?
I do not yet, okay.
Oh my God, I can try one more time.
Oh, good God.
Okay, I'm trying to do something special for you guys.
Hold on
Hey, summer love summer loving had me a blast
I was a little bit a little bit. Um, I'm sorry
Summer loving had me a blast. There we go
I met a girl for razies can be she met a guy as cute as me
Summer days
Drifted away. Oh, I'm sorry. I don't want I hope that wasn't offensive to anybody
Oh, what did a revolver read? Okay, so guys, I'm gonna take a bet right now
I bet he said the n-word backstage. You're not gonna see the bet to see if he said the n-word
How much does he want to bet me? Can you can someone if if if he says the n-word if you said the n-word in the back stage
Or so I think he did okay. I'm just predicted can someone send me a cash up so I can
Prime my sour as a way over a couple drinks
Um
Yeah, he I mean he didn't say the M word exactly but he said he was close enough I would say he made some kind of cult reference
And now he's gone. I
Mean he's not even a cult member. I
Mean at least the people with wrenches that they're cult members. I mean, it's like they're in the cult. I have a death
I think I'm the only
Yeah, Barbara summer
Profiler Reds, you know nothing next to his name not a breed not a mod not a member
It comes up demanding full panel privileges. I mean some people are just sad, you know, that's my coffee
I did
my gosh, well, maybe I'll have to go instead of a
Alcohol time I'll just have some more McDonald's, but I do have a I have a secret McDonald's
Well, let me just have a secret secret stash of food McDonald's that they'll keep me then for the rest of the month
But okay anyway
It's called the monopoly. Yeah, okay. Wait, wait, you guys are mad at me. I mean, come on
Be mad at me
How can you be mad at me? Look how cute I am
I'm really cute
Um
Okay, well, anyway, I think I can get a tobacco hit off of the stuff off my table. Hold on a second. Let me just
I'm sorry. This isn't it. It's not very
Not what I like to be doing
You know tobacco is like one of the worst addictions in the world. Okay. Okay. What do I got here? Do I got tobacco? I do have plenty of it, okay?
So, yeah plenty of it. It's almost the ash.
I see some tobacco in there. There are some, there are some, there's some brown leaves. Okay.
You know the great thing is if I find it a cigar or a cigarette butt or something. I don't feel a little bit pretty good at cleaning.
Okay, here you go. Bottoms up guys.
Mmm, that'll do pig that'll do pig that I came from babe. It's a lot from babe means it's okay. It's perfect
Hey, we'll see
Anyway, I can actually probably dig up another dollar and change and have it all okay. Yeah, and good
This this video gonna freeze again. How are we doing in chat?
People if I wasn't nobody before Benny Blanca, but now I have a cult. Yeah, I was no before Benny
Yeah, now I have a cult now. I'm bigger than Benny. Okay, so what?
So what what's your point?
Another cult member it gets the same people. It's called right
Is eating static whispering your eyes and traffic they crawl through my circuits chanting reverse like angels the flunk their universe
This is my own call. I get to make this call.
Apparently there's new stuff for the little chat box.
Let me see if I can fix it.
Oh, yeah, there it is, okay.
Oh, look, I made it wide, and we get tall too.
Okay, I'll make it wide, I'll make it big.
How's that, that better?
Now I can read it better.
Okay, guys, I'm gonna keep this,
I don't have to keep my screen small.
Okay, guys, who wants a reading?
I'll do quick free readings.
I'll do longer ones for a tip and cash out.
Casey, if you want to get like several readings,
like two $10 readings and a $5 reading,
that would pay off your thing.
Cause I know you want to go on the show so bad
and you just want to annoy me until I do it.
So why don't you just buy some readings?
If you just buy $1, $10 one tonight,
I will consider that a down payment.
But if not, I don't want to hear it again, and you're going to be very quickly hit into the chat.
Okay.
I mean, very quickly.
My finger is on the trigger tonight.
Okay.
$10.
They'll get you back in tonight.
And you'll get a reading on the panel, so they'll give you something to talk about.
Get
Psyche's and ropes but wife is divine we stream
With super chat pricing
Just online
Cult
Cult Sake
Yeah
Enlightenments Merge Size Medium
We drink the algorithms while
I don't know if you're in trouble, like I'm not mad at you ever, but he said he has time stamps of
some woman's show where you appear on the bad mouth to me. Okay, this version now. Okay, okay, one, two,
four, oh, okay. Okay, five parts for you Chanel.
Okay, so now you're coming out of this or coming from this Queen of Wands energy. Oh, can we see it? Yeah
I need to turn off my backdrop a little bit. It's a little bit distracting. I'm so sorry. Okay
There we go, okay
Coming through from this Queen of Wands energy, which is like very good energy. I don't know if you are a fire sun
but this is about courage confidence independence and determination and so you've really come from these qualities and I guess you're
Working with this man or about to it looks like a more recent man, maybe but it's an ultimate authority rest with him
Okay, dealing with a very powerful man this Emperor power
Okay
I don't know if this is your husband or it's like some kind of powerful man that you're dealing with I do see
You've got a couple pages in this reading too. Okay, you got a page of sword and the page of pentacles
So there's some kind of new beginning both intellectually and well page of swords too
I mean the page of pentacles is financially right but the page of swords is really about intellectual
But it's also about it could be like somebody you spying or somebody spying on you too. Okay
There's also it looks like the eight of sorrows. This is like, you know, you are maybe stuck in your head about something
You have to realize that it's just mental constraints. You're putting on yourself. It's not like you need a real constraint
Okay, so you can get out of that
Six of cups and the way to get out of that it looks like it's some kind of like nostalgia
Okay, or even like lip like through your own kids like there's when we're gonna be like happy nostalgia the happy memories
Also, you're coming up as the Empress as well. You will like come through with all all these um
All these elements mastered
The real deal queen, right? There's all the queens in the deck actually and finally I have one more for you
Okay, um, we got this uh four pentacles a collector. Okay, maybe collecting something collecting some evidence or collecting something
that will um
I almost see redeem you or like, or, you know,
give the truth about something,
relate the truth about something
that people maybe thought correctly about you.
Hope you like that Chanel.
Anyone would like to come up on panel?
Okay.
Two hours, 48, 10, 27.
I wanna see that 248.
Let's pull it up.
I'm not mad, and I'm not gonna get mad at you,
I understand this, like, you know,
when you're on other shows.
People say things and I'm mad. I just want to see what was said like just like so I'm not like some of the chuch in the dark about
What's being said about me?
So it's called panel verse vogs
Pose yesterday, I think I don't know if they have the yesterday's on I don't know if it's up yet. Let me see
So the most recent one I have is for beta is
I wish I was like you easily amused.
I don't know if this is the one.
Let me check.
I know I saw Mason in this one earlier.
We'd pull up two hours 48.
Okay, let's have a look.
Two hours 48.
Oh, I see time.
I see time.
Hold on. Guys, this is a revelation.
That's how confident I am that she doesn't need help.
Yeah, no doubt Garrett. I mean shit happens, right? People die. I know it's it's it's unfortunate people die people die
I mean
Really, we really don't die. We just
Regardless regardless. We're no longer available to do stuff in this life
We die from we die from one university move ourselves into a new one a
hairline
Sweet Pete. I mean, I remember
All of them and then we start over from my hairline baby
Through my horn you move into another dimension or another form of life
I mean, I don't think life stops after death. I think that that's not a picture of me
That's a picture of a cat with a top hat is life. Oh, not stop
But the thing that is you I'm I think stops
No, I think that yeah, I think I agree. The thing that is what you're what you're doing
Everybody
If we're building a house, of course, we ain't gonna be just continuing to build a house after we die because we're dead
But I mean even to go a little further. I even mean when I say that I even mean the spirit
I don't think that there is an afterlife myself
Okay, so another atheist in the world doesn't care about the after that just cares about
this.
Okay.
What we are is nothing but it.
I really don't know how to.
I think these are the kind of dumbest point where I'm sorry, it makes any sense to anybody
but.
Um, not just one second.
Can anybody answer what's going on with like you's airline.
I haven't even looked over there.
Know what's going on
What
Somebody share the screen and show it up
Oh my time
Time mine was a meant to make it meant to be oh everyone was in it. Oh, yeah, thank you school guy
You can share the screen, you can share the screen.
Get it big, let's see the whole thing.
Let's see my big stupid head.
Who's the owner of the stream?
Or she's the one on the left?
She's gone, we don't know where she is.
She's disappeared into the void.
I'm just laughing at his profile.
Look at the profile picture.
Yeah, yeah, I see it.
I know, well, it's what, but...
What is going on with his hairline?
I was wearing a headphone so the hair was pulled back a little bit, you see the big headphones
I'm wearing?
That's the thing like she hasn't even spoken in chat, that's what makes me think her phone
is completely dead.
I'm fine.
Well, how long has she been gone if her phone's dead for more than 12 minutes and she's not
dead?
I mean, that's enough. It's just dumb, you know.
Chanel, did you hear your reading? I'm sorry, Chanel, but I hope I didn't keep you waiting too long.
Yeah, I mean it is making fun of me on another panel and he's a mod to like why is my mod like going oh look at how
Stupid psyche looks like like why like why is that and I don't come I'm actually like you know
It was the cult of psyche at this point
So you should be more of a kind of like look what if a member of someone's cult was like going to make going making fun of their leader
But they'd be in the cult much longer
I'm just starting to think.
Even if it was like good nature,
oh, it may be true, like, is my hairline in the mess?
Like, what, like, what, at most, cold leaders,
like, when it's occupies me, you weren't trying to mean,
okay, well, why don't you show it on my show?
You can do it, like, in the chat here,
where it's actually like, you know,
maybe that someone's gonna find it funnier,
but like, Ambedez are just gonna say,
oh, I look like some kind of longaloid, you know,
like, my head is a weird shape,
my hairline's a weird shape, I'm going bald.
I mean, I have a fine hairline, I'm not, whatever.
I don't know.
Oh, yeah, I mean it's like what you're close. It's just like God got you like God
He's like, oh, I'm your friend and stuff and then he puts up like, you know picture of me looking dumb and stuff it's like
Can't you like play with your own photos and I've had my own photo
I've had my own
Reputation of photo all kinds of stuff. It's okay. I don't care
Just like but that's what you really think of me. I'm just like some kind of joke. It's fine
Obviously, I am so kind of joke because it's like people won't even like you know donate for like a reading or anything and like you know
If I ask me, you know, please then it's like I'm begging for fish tacos or something like that
and all I'm trying to do is like, you know survive but
Anyway, well now I'm kind of depressed and like, you know, I'm probably gonna go back to bed
but you know, thanks for being here and everything and
Nice night